<questionnaire>
    <title>Questionnaire for new users</title>
    <description>When the user first opens an app — he should be introduced with a questionnaire to
        assess better his goals, fitness level, etc. He has an ability to skip the questionnaire</description>
    <flow>
        <on-start>
            When the app starts, it should check if the user has answered questionnaire in the local
            storage(hive) or if he decided to skip it. if he has answered or if he decided to skip -
            navigate to main screen. Otherwise - navigate to questionnaire page. Doesn't matter if
            the user is logged in or no - this should be the first screen he sees
        </on-start>
        <on-questionnaire-begin-view>
            The first screen the user should see should have a brief explanation of why the
            questionnaire is important and how it will help tailor the app experience to his needs.
            Say that it contains 12 questions including this one, and takes 3-5 minutes on average.
            Then, at the bottom there should be two buttons: "Start" or "do it later". Update the choice in local storage
        </on-questionnaire-begin-view>
        <questionnaire-view>
            <section> Goals &amp; Experience <question>
                    <title>
                        What is your primary fitness goal? (Select one)
                    </title>
                    <options>
                        <option>
                            Increase muscle size (Hypertrophy)
                        </option>
                        <option>
                            Increase strength (Lifting heavier weights)
                        </option>
                        <option>
                            Improve cardiovascular endurance
                        </option>
                        <option>
                            Lose weight / Fat loss
                        </option>
                        <option>
                            Improve overall health and fitness
                        </option>
                        <option>
                            Recover from an injury (Rehabilitation)
                        </option>
                    </options>
                </question>
                <question>
                    <title>What is your current level of workout experience? (Select one)</title>
                    <options>
                        <option>Beginner (Little to no experience)</option>
                        <option>Intermediate (I have been working out consistently for at least 6
                months.)</option>
                        <option>Advanced (I have been consistently training for over 2 years.)</option>
                    </options>
                </question>
            </section>
            <section> Health &amp; Safety <question>
                    <title>Have you been diagnosed with any of the following health conditions?
                (Select all that apply):</title>
                    <options>
                        <option>Heart disease</option>
                        <option>High blood pressure</option>
                        <option>Diabetes</option>
                        <option>Joint conditions (e.g., arthritis)</option>
                        <option>Respiratory issues (e.g., asthma)</option>
                        <option>Prefer not to say</option>
                        <option>I have none of the above</option>
                    </options>
                </question>
                <question>
                    <title>Do you have any current or past injuries that affect your ability to
                exercise?</title>
                    <options>
                        <option>Shoulder</option>
                        <option>Lower back</option>
                        <option>Knee</option>
                        <option>Ankle</option>
                        <option>Wrist</option>
                        <option>Prefer not to say</option>
                        <option>I have no injuries</option>
                    </options>
                </question>
            </section>
            <section> Availability &amp; Preferences <question>
                    <title>How many days per week can you commit to working out?</title>
                    <options>
                        <option>1-2 days</option>
                        <option>3-4 days</option>
                        <option>5-7 days</option>
                    </options>
                </question>
                <question>
                    <title>How long are your typical workout sessions?</title>
                    <options>
                        <option>Less than 30 minutes</option>
                        <option>30-60 minutes</option>
                        <option>60-90 minutes</option>
                        <option>More than 90 minutes</option>
                    </options>
                </question>
                <question>
                    <title>Which types of exercise do you enjoy?</title>
                    <options>
                        <option>Weightlifting / Strength training</option>
                        <option>Bodyweight exercises</option>
                        <option>Running / Jogging</option>
                        <option>Swimming</option>
                        <option>Cycling</option>
                        <option>Yoga / Pilates</option>
                        <option>Team sports</option>
                    </options>
                </question>
            </section>
            <section>
                <question>
                    <title>Do you have access to a gym or workout equipment?</title>
                    <options>
                        <option>Yes, I have access to a fully equipped gym</option>
                        <option>Yes, I have some basic equipment at home (e.g., dumbbells,
                            resistance bands)</option>
                        <option>No, I prefer bodyweight exercises or outdoor activities</option>
                    </options>
                </question>
            </section>
        </questionnaire-view>
        <on-completion>
            After the user completes the questionnaire or decides to skip it - save his choice in
            local storage(hive), send it over api to back end and navigate to main screen
        </on-completion>
    </flow>
    <UI>
        Don't put everything on one screen - split it into multiple sections with one question per
        view; with a progress indicator at the top. Each section should have a "Next" button to
        proceed to the next question and "Back" button to return to the previous one. At the end of
        the questionnaire, provide a "Submit" button to finalize the responses.
    </UI>
</questionnaire>