<save-workout>
    <description>
        Saves the free workout just performed
    </description>
    <flow>
        <well_done_workout_screen>
            The following functionality applies only to the well_done_workout_screen if the user has performed free workout.
            <feature id="1">
                <UI>
                    Button 'Save Workout'
                </UI>
                <functionality>
                    Move to 'save_workout_screen.dart' with just performed exercise.
                </functionality>
            </feature>
        </well_done_workout_screen>
        <save_workout_screen>
            <feature id="1">
                <UI>
                    Render the workout that a user has just performed in a list with adjustable fields. Exercise-by-exercise.
                </UI>
            </feature>
            <feature id="2">
                <UI>
                    Every tile of list should contain exercise's name, amount of sets, reps time for breaks and average weight. Also, at the top right there should be a trash icon.
                </UI>
                <functionality>
                    By pressing on the trash icon, remove the exercise from the list.
                </functionality>
            </feature>
            <feature id="3">
                <UI>
                    An open exercise panel
                </UI>
                <functionality>
                    by pressing on the exercise, a panel should open to adjust the amount of sets, amount of reps/set, rest time and the weight.
                </functionality>
            </feature>
            <feature id="4">
                <UI>
                    button "Continue"
                </UI>
                <functionality>
                    By pressing on "Continue" button a quick form to fill in the name and description(optional)
                </functionality>
            </feature>
            <feature id="5">
                <UI>name field</UI>
                <functionality>
                    The field should be one-lined only with english letters, no more than 100 symbols, no less than 6 letters. no special characters
                </functionality>
            </feature>
            <feature id="6">
                <UI>description field</UI>
                <functionality>
                    The field should be multi-lined only with english letters, no more than 200 symbols, no less than 10 letters. no special characters
                </functionality>
            </feature>
            <feature id="7">
                <UI>OutlinedButton "Back"</UI>
                <functionality>
                    Pressing on the button, it returns to selecting exercises with the swipe.
                </functionality>
            </feature>
            <feature id="8">
                <UI>at the bottom Button "Save"</UI>
                <functionality>
                    Pressing on the button, it creates a `createCustomWorkout` request(see `workout_api_service.dart`). If successful, show a toast Created a custom workout with button "Go Home" and either way navigate home after 3 seconds. If unsuccessful, create toast "Something went wrong. Try again later" or something like this, with a button "Go Home".
                </functionality>
            </feature>
        </save_workout_screen>
    </flow>
    <reporting>
        After completion of every feature, report about it.
    </reporting>
    <general-instructions>
        Every tab in flow has multiple screens. If this screen exists in the codebase, then you need to edit it. If the screen does not exist - create it. If you think you need to create an extra screen, model, component, etc. - create it.
    </general-instructions>
</save-workout>